<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Personal | Spencer L Willardson</title>
    <link>/category/personal/</link>
      <atom:link href="/category/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Personal</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© Spencer L Willardson 2020</copyright><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/images/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_2.png</url>
      <title>Personal</title>
      <link>/category/personal/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Control of my Blogging and Website</title>
      <link>/post/taking-control-of-my-blogging-and-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/post/taking-control-of-my-blogging-and-website/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is my inagaural post on my new website.  I have set up a website using Rstudio and the &amp;lsquo;Blogdown&amp;rsquo; package with the Hugo-Academic theme.  I have had a website for 12 years, but always one that was a &amp;ldquo;point and click&amp;rdquo; model. All of my sites have been powered by and limited by the options of the Google Sites framework. That isn&amp;rsquo;t a bad option, but I wanted something that looked a bit more elegant, and which could fit in with my workflow, which has increasingly moved to R and RStudio over the past few years.  I built the website as a way to build up my skillset. I am particularly excited about the opportunity to share snippets of work, to blog more regularly and with greater power, and to have a slick-looking website.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am still getting the hang of things.  I added and adjusted all my personal information and added my publications.  I am looking forward to populating my 
&lt;a href=&#34;../../Teaching&#34;&gt;Teaching&lt;/a&gt; and 
&lt;a href=&#34;../../Research&#34;&gt;Research&lt;/a&gt; sections.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After I get all of my academic information transferred and updated on this website, I&amp;rsquo;ll also begin blogging some of my thoughts about academia, my experiences in war, and other things that interest me.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
